本字幕由YYeTs人人影视字幕翻译制作
禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多字幕 影视 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译: 阿蘅  慕风夕 VK  Asleep 小Q
校对: 天意 后期：csbeyond 波多  之间
他们喊的是我的名字
一  二
欢迎收看Taylor Swift的无畏之旅
You belong with me
这是一个从小就怀揣远大理想的小女孩的故事
从最早这样的表演
Twinkle twinkle little star
确实确实是很小的时候
再到人生第一个转折点
那是我第一次当着那么多人唱歌
演出非常成功
前进道路上满是荆棘
我有一段时间  没有朋友
作为她的妈妈  听说他人对自己孩子都避而远之
心里很不是滋味的
她那时并不知道
但是即使在孩提时期  Taylor也是无畏的
大家好  我是Taylor  我11岁
我想签约  给我打电话吧  会有惊喜哦
我们会向您揭示《Fearless》专辑的制作过程
分享你们喜爱的歌曲背后的灵感
这首歌是关于分手的故事
是我的真实经历
和Taylor一起见证她的第一次巡回演出
接下来的三个晚上
从台前到幕后  跟随Taylor的步伐
一起分享她的无畏之旅
《Taylor Swift的无畏之旅》
If you could see that I'm the one who understands you
You Belong With Me
Been here all along so why can't you see
You belong with me
You're on the phone with your girlfriend, she's upset
She's going off about something that you said
'Cuz she doesn't get your humor like I do
I'm in the room, it's a typical Tuesday night
I'm listening to the kind of music she doesn't like
And she'll never know your story like I do
But she wears short skirts
I wear T-shirts
She's cheer captain
And I'm on the bleachers
Dreaming about the day when you wake up
And find what you're looking for
Has been here the whole time
If you could see that I'm the one who understands you
Been here all along so why can't you see
You belong with me
Walkin' the streets with you and your worn-out jeans
I can't help thinking this is how it ought to be
Laughing on a park bench, thinking to myself
Hey isn't this easy
And you've got a smile that could light up this whole town
I haven't seen it in a while since she brought you down
You say you're fine
I know you better then that
Hey whatcha doing with a girl like that
She wears high heels
I wear sneakers.
She's cheer captain and I'm on the bleachers
Dreaming about the day when you wake up and find
That what you're looking for
Has been here the whole time
If you could see that I'm the one who understands you
Been here all along so why can't you see
You belong with me
Standing by and waiting at your back door
All this time how could you not know
Baby
You belong with me
I remember you drivin'to my house
In the middle of the night
I'm the one who makes you laugh
When you know you're about to cry
And I know your favorite songs
And you tell me about your dreams
Think I know where you belong
Think I know it's with me
Can't you see that I'm the one who understands you
Been here all along
So why can't you see
you belong with me
Standing by and waiting at your back door
All this time
How could you not know
Baby
you belong with me
Have you ever thought just maybe
《Taylor Swift的无畏之旅》
欢迎继续收看节目
精彩尽在HUB台
《Taylor Swift的无畏之旅》
Twinkle twinkle little star
从我特别小的时候开始我就喜欢音乐
印象最深的是夏天去海滩的时候
我会到处跑  边跑边唱
Taylor
我八九岁的时候
得到我人生中的第一把吉他
那时我还无法学弹吉他
因为我的手太小了
虽然吉他一直在我身边
但被我弃置在角落里
当我12岁的时候
神奇的事情发生了
我父母请了一个人来修我的电脑
那时我正在做作业
他看到了角落那把吉他
他问我"你弹吉他么"
我说"没有  我想弹  但是...不能"
他说"你想要我教你么"
我说"好啊  太好了"
自那以后  我就对吉他爱不释手了
我一有空就写歌
我记得我写的第一首完整的歌叫Lucky You
写的是一个敢于与众不同的女孩
那个时候  她就是  写自己
我常常被取笑  常常被嘲笑
我那个时候  没有朋友
其他小女孩都忙着玩寄宿之夜
或者玩足球
而Taylor只想登台演出
这与大家格格不入
译注: 费城76人队 NBA球队 主场:Wachovia Center
2002年4月5日 费城七六人队主场
我站在巨大的篮球场中央演唱
身着印有美国国旗的亮片T恤
白色牛仔裤  还戴了红色发箍
一副爱国者的形象
我这辈子从没那么紧张过
再次感谢  Taylor Swift
演出被当地报纸大肆报道
第二天上学的时候
招来别人的各种羡慕嫉妒恨
那天最难受的是
当我去接Taylor放学的时候
我知道这一天她也许过得很难
我会对发生的事有所耳闻
但对于一位妈妈来说
听到这种事发生在学校  心里很难过
午饭时  只要有她坐的地方
大家都会远远躲开
对于家长来说
没什么比看到孩子受伤更让人心疼的事了
你想要帮她讨还公道
但我知道  这是她不得不经历的事
在我脑中
这个叫纳什维尔的地方是我的圆梦之地
无数音乐人才在那里被挖掘出来
我对自己说  纳什维尔  我一定要去
我大概求了父母整整一年
带我去纳什维尔吧
不断恳求
我想去纳什维尔
百折不挠
说话总离不开这件事
就当是休息一下
我们去纳什维尔  看看结果如何
每一个到纳什维尔的人
都和我当时的梦想一样
那就是  成为一个艺术家
想要上台表演  下面座无虚席
看啊  那是水星唱片公司
快停车
我要把样带给他们听听
我下车走进去  自我介绍
我叫Taylor  今年11岁
我想要签约
请给我电话  会有惊喜哦
我知道自己要找到一种与众不同的风格
耳目一新的
更具内涵的
要想让我快乐
绝不能少了音乐
我可以连续弹上几个小时吉他
直到弹到手指流血
她从不放下吉他
她也从不愿放下吉他
我们不得不命令她
把吉他放下  吃完晚饭再弹
在那时候  让她放下吉他成了一个很棘手的问题
我完全爱上了音乐
你正在收看的是HUB台
马上回来
我们在Taylor拿到发展合同后
决定搬到纳什维尔去
作为父母  我们很自豪
觉得应该支持她到最有发展前途的领域中去
13岁的时候
我和RCA接触
他们和我签订发展合同
我们看好你  但也有担心
看看发展再说
并不是要给你出专辑
我和Taylor一周去一次
带着她写的新曲
他们看后会说  不错
还像回事
但他们从没说
就是这首  这是很棒的曲子
我们出专辑吧
在年底的时候
他们有机会和我签约
也可以不签约再观察一年
但是他们说
我们还不想冒险给她出专辑
我做了一件在纳什维尔算是大胆的事
我们和公司大吵一架  然后走人了
因为我感觉没机会做自己的音乐了
所以走得干脆
我很慌张
这可是知名唱片公司啊
这种机会可不是每天都有机会遇到的
你真的要走吗
她毫不犹豫说是
我在蓝鸟咖啡屋演出
讽刺的是
在那里他们发现了Faith Hill
我弹唱了几首自己写的歌
观众中有个叫Scott的人
演出结束后他找到我
他说  我想给你出专辑
我要你用自己写的歌曲
我激动极了
后来他打电话约我见面谈
好消息是  我想给你出唱片
坏消息是  我还没有唱片公司
他向我解释
他没有办公大楼
也没想好公司名称
只是有这样一个梦想
你能等我实现这些吗
不知为什么
我决定相信他
她放心将专辑交给这个人做
而这个人也相信她会有所作为
如果我能和这家公司一起成长
做这家公司的第一位签约歌手
我并不介意
只要能完成我冒险  大胆  创新的心愿
所以我和Scott Borchetta签约了
出了一张专辑  里面都是我自己写的歌
这个红色的小东西
能够屏蔽杂音
是最棒的器材
像这样的声音  都会屏蔽掉
棒极了
这种情况下  没有人看好我们
但我们却很有信心
出第一张单曲的时候
我非常激动
因为我不知道会不会成功
我还记得自己把专辑装入信封
和妈妈一起把这些送到电台
跑了好多个电台
你一定以为是坐旅游车吧
不是  租了一辆车而已
只有一个游客
就是躺在后排的我
Big 98 WSIX
2009年9月8日
你好  甜心
最近怎么样
很好
我给你带曲奇来了
这是你做的
Taylor Swift
自制曲奇
敬请品尝
走访了无数个电台
每次去电台
我都会在会议室为几个DJ演唱
求他们为我广播
这很有效
我的专辑第一周卖出了39,000张
之后销售量直线飙升
后来发生的事情远远超乎预料
我和所有想象的到的
乡村音乐明星见面
Brad Paisley
Kenny Chesney
Tim Mcgraw
和他们同台演出
我紧张至极
反复排练
我很享受那种感觉
那是我最怀念的日子之一
这首歌我很喜欢
如果你手里有手机  荧光棒
或者任何能够发光的东西
举起来让我看到
我希望大家和我一起唱
因为这是这是我被大家所熟知的第一首歌
You said the way my blue eyes shined
Put those Georgia stars to shame that night
I said, that's a lie
Just a boy in a Chevy truck
That had a tendency of getting stuck
On backroads at night
And I was right there beside him
All summer long
And then the time we woke up to Find that summer'd gone
But when you think, Tim McGraw
I hope you think my favorite song
The one we danced to all night long
The moon like a spotlight on the lake
When you think happiness
I hope you think that little black dress
Think of my head on your chest
And my old faded blue jeans
When you think Tim McGraw
I hope you think of me
September saw a month of tears
And thanking God that you weren't here
To see me like that
But in a box beneath my bed
Is a letter that you never read
From three summers back
It's hard not to find it all a little bitter sweet
And looking back on all of that It's nice to believe
When you think, Tim McGraw
I hope you think my favorite song
The one we danced to all night long
The moon like a spotlight on the lake
When you think happiness
I hope you think, that little black dress
Think of my head on your chest
And my old faded blue jeans
When you think Tim McGraw
I hope you think of me
穿过那层层人群感觉真的太好了
人们都在尖叫
我自己也很喜欢使别人兴奋
那真的是我最爱做的事
那首歌唱完后
我下台拥抱了好多好多人
我向那些头一次来看演唱会的孩子表达爱意
到台下去到人群中去
向他们打招呼
感谢他们前来捧场
站在那儿和他们近距离的接触
这些对我来说真的非常重要
因为我一直想跟他们走近些
因为我无法相信
没有了他们我还能走多远
在我做过的所有事情中
那真的是我最爱做的一件了
And I'm back for the first time since then
I'm standing on your street
And there's a letter left on your doorstep
And the first thing that you'll read
Is, when you think, Tim McGraw
I hope you think my favorite song
Turn your stand radio on
I hope it takes you back to that place
When you think happiness
I hope you think that little black dress
Think of my head on your chest
And my old faded blue jeans
When you think Tim McGraw
I hope you think of me
Oh, think of me
Whoo-o-o-o-o
You said the way my blue eyes shined
Put those Georgia stars to shame that night
I said, that's a lie
我真的很喜欢上学
我很庆幸自己上了高中
所有的孩子都很好
我也不是头一次被当成怪物了
他们真的从没在意过我
想成为一名歌手的梦想
九年级开学的第一天
初次踏进高中校园
我的第一节课坐在一个红发女孩儿旁边
我们立刻就成为了好朋友
因为我们都是那种在英语课上
很鬼马的人
我们彼此惺惺相惜
为相同的事情兴奋或开心
我们的目标也相同
我们非常合得来
她成为我写完歌后的首个听众
我真的非常非常珍惜那些时光
有人愿意为我演奏她的新歌
那是我和她在一起中最美好的一段时光
做她喜爱的事情
看她那样激情地唱歌
我会去她家
坐在她房间里唱歌给她听
她就像个超级啦啦队长
我每次夸她  她都表现的很震惊
一脸惊讶的样子
真的吗  谢谢你  太谢谢你了
她总是心存感激
我想写首关于我俩共同经历的歌
当我们过完15岁
成为一名高中新生
你就像是在一个巨大的世界里遨游
十六七岁  对女生来说
那是最艰难的岁月
因为那时你得给自己定位
努力认识自己
你在高中校园里就像是沧海一粟一样
当你一路艰难的走来
也学会了很多
You take a deep breath
And you walk through the doors
It's the morning of your very first day
You say hi to your friends
You ain't seen in a while
Try and stay out of everybodys' way
It's your freshman year
And you're gonna be here
For the next four years in this town
Hoping one of those senior boys Will wink at you and say
You know I haven't seen you around
Before
Cause when you're fifteen
Somebody tells you they love you
You're gonna believe them
And when you're fifteen
Feeling like there're
Nothing to figure out
Well count to ten, take it in
This is life before
Who you're gonna be fifteen
You sit in class next to a redhead named Abigail
And soon enough you're best friends
Laughing at the other girls
Who thinks they're so cool
Will be out of here as soon as we can
我记得第一次对Abigail唱这首歌
还只是吉他版本的
她被震惊了
我觉得难以置信
这首歌非常打动人
直到现在也是如此
Your mum's waiting up
And you're thinking that he's the one
And you dance around your room when the night ends
When the night ends
Cause when you're fifteen
在这首歌里讲述的
是她的一个很私人的故事
非常原始和真实
每个人都在问我
这首歌会不会冒犯到我
一点也没有
因为身处于听众之中
看到大家与歌曲产生共鸣
正是我所期待的
Makes your head spin round
But in your life
You'll do things greater than
Dating the boy on the football team
I didn't know it at fifteen
When all you wanted is to be wanted
Wish you could go back
And tell yourself what you know now
Back then I swore
I was gonna marry him someday
But I realize some bigger dreams of mine
And Abigail gave everything she had to a boy
Who changed his mind and we both cried
我很荣幸她会谈到我
还有我的经历
并且写在歌里
与无数的人分享
关于这首歌我最高兴的事情是
她对此感到骄傲
也许她的故事能够帮助别的女孩
为命运做出正确的选择
To look before you fall
就像歌里写的那样
能够三思而后行
I've found that time can heal most anything
And you just might find who you're supposed to be
I didn't know who I was supposed to be
At fifteen
Your very first day
You take a deep breath girl
Take a deep breath
As you walk through the doors
我第一张专辑的大部分歌曲
灵感都是来自高中生活
我有首歌叫《You belong with me》
就是关于对学校里的女生
感到生气的歌曲
因为她是啦啦队队长
学校里最受欢迎的女孩
而你自己却是无名之辈
对我而言
高中时期只是坐在那里
感知身边的一切
就让我学到了很多
我的那首《Teardrops on my guitar》
是彻底地坦白自己爱上了某个人
曾经有段时间
出现了一个男孩
于是我在歌里写到这个男孩
然后在歌里给他取了个名字
而这个男孩
在教室里曾经坐在我旁边
当我对某个人产生迷恋的时候
我就会在我的歌里给他取名字
这感觉就像你迫不及待要到他面前
告诉他你的感觉
告诉他你是谁
好吧我承认
我完全爱上了这个男孩
但是他甚至不知道我的存在
但是日复一日
他都会来教室
而且日复一日
他都坐在我的身边
有时候他甚至会和我讲话
但是讲的是他的女朋友
所以我一直没告诉他
我喜欢他
但是我写了一首有关他的歌
我猜现在他应该知道了
Drew looks at me
用Drew这个名字
大家都知道我说的是谁了
《Teardrops on my guitar》
What I want and I need
And everything that we should be
I'll bet she's beautiful
That girl he talks about
And she's got everything
That I have to live without
我不敢相信
这是我第一次看到她
在歌曲中这么深入地表达了自己
I laugh cause it's just so funny
I can't even see
Anyone when he's with me
He says he's so in love
He's finally got it right
I wonder if he knews
He's all I think about at night
He's the reason for the teardrops on my guitar
The only thing that keeps me wishing on a wishing star
He's the song in the car I keep singing
Don't know why I do
Drew walks by me
Can he tell that I can't breathe
And there he goes so perfectly
The kind of flawless I wish I could be
She better hold him tight
Give him all her love
Look in those beautiful eyes
And know she's lucky cause
He's the reason for the teardrops on my guitar
The only thing that keeps me wishing on a wishing star
He's the song in the car I keep singing
Don't know why I do
而这个叫Drew的男孩
在大约一年半后出现在我的车道上
我不知道
有时候真的很尴尬
没错  那状况真的很尴尬
我想她一定很震惊
我们都有些吃惊
谁能想到这发生的一切呢
So I drive home alone
As I turn out the light
I'll put his picture down
And maybe get some sleep tonight
'Cuz he's the reason for the teardrops on my guitar
The only one who's got enough of me to break my heart
He's the song in the car I keep singing
Don't know why I do
He's the time taken up but there's never enough
And he's all that I need to fall into
Drew looks at me, I fake a smile so he won't see
今天早些时候我们进行了排演
现在  要飞去纽约
在那边呆一晚
为明天做准备
发行唱片前的那几天
简直就是  忙疯了
行程爆满  忙得不得了
这辈子疯狂的一天啊
《Fearless》那张专辑发行前夕
我俩相视  发现
她真的是活在自己的梦里
Taylor Swift
天呐
见到你太幸福了
今天实在忙抽了
差一刻五点就爬起来
做头发化妆  一通折腾
之后赶去上《早安美国》的节目
到那之后
做一些表演啊  采访什么的
然后离开赶去MTV
在那里做一堆新闻采访
嗨  Trisha  我爱你  生日快乐
之后又赶去WPLJ
Taylor Swift
谢谢大家来捧场  太给力了
新唱片今天就要发行了
我真的超激动
再之后呢
我们又去David Letterman的秀场
那是我第一次在那里表演
感觉超棒的
我无比期待Letterman的脱口秀
那个秀总是各种欢乐
用笛子吹《Fearless》真的很有趣
现在我上了飞机  准备回家
去买我自己的CD
午夜的时候
唱片终于发了
我当时在亨德森商店
23点59分  我们现在要去买唱片了
真的很激动
当时好多人在那里
都激动地尖叫
谢谢你们赶来支持
真的非常感谢
他们都在买唱片
我自己也有买
大伙都在这上倾注了无数心血
现在它终于发行了
当时真的很疯狂
商店里摆满自己的CD
大家从四面八方赶来
和我一起买
真的是很有趣的经历
永生难忘
我真的很爱你们
谢谢你们来到这里
第一时间收藏我的第二张专辑
晚安  我爱你们
现在我终于
终于不用再到处跑了
我躺在飞机上
这一天终于完了
这是我经历过的最长的一天
《Fearless》这张唱片出来以后
第一周就卖到了596000张
我真的高兴得不得了
还记得我第一张唱片出来的时候
首周卖到了39000张
就把我吓坏了
这次卖到了596000张
真的是个不小的飞跃
I was riding shotgun with my hair undone in the front seat of his car
He's got a one-hand feel on the steering wheel
The other on my heart
I look around, turn the radio down
He says baby is something wrong
I say nothing I was just thinking how we don't have a song
And he says
Our song is the slamming screen door,
Sneakin' out late, tapping on your window
When you're on the phone and you talk real slow
Cause it's late and your mama don't know
Our song is the way you laugh
The first date "man, I didn't kiss her, but I should have"
And when I got home ... before I said amen
Asking God if he could play it again
I was walking up the front porch steps after everything the day
Had gone all wrong or been trampled on
And lost and thrown away
Got to the hallway, well on my way to my lovin' bed
I almost didn't notice all the roses
And the note that said...
Cause our song is the slamming screen door
Sneaking out late, tapping on his window
When we're on the phone and he talks real slow
Cause it's late and his mama don't know
Our song is the way he laughs
The first date "man, I didn't kiss him, and I could have"
And when I got home, before I said amen
Asking God if he could play it again
i've heard every album, listened to the radio
waited for something to come along
that was as good as our song
cause our song is the slamming screen door
sneaking out late, tapping on his window
when we're on the phone and he talks real slow
cause it's late and his mama don't know
our song is the way he laughs
the first date "man, i didn't kiss him, and i should have"
and when i got home, before i said amen
asking god if he could play it again
play it again
i was riding shotgun with my hair undone
in the front seat of his car
i grabbed a pen and an old napkin
and i wrote down our song
明天
与Taylor Swift一起
进驻无畏之旅第二站
梦想真的会实现
和我一起回到舞台上
来认识所有力挺我走过这无畏之旅的朋友们
Taylor Swift无畏之旅  中集
明晚七点  HUB独家首播
勇者无畏